Kitana history here you're gonna walk
the red line north enemy see the
historical stuff so the day will tell
the story yeah I'm good at that
hi Michael Mary yes yeah three years
could tell so at the Isabel the Isabella
Stewart Gardner Museum museum a few
blocks away from where we are right now
yeah it's about a very eccentric woman
she was sort of like I'm gonna wear a
headband I know women wear headbands and
she thought that life I'm going to do
something awesome and so she built this
museum I mean she had like a thousands
of his heart that were from the Greece
most expensive like places of world so
do you want me to go to 1990 the story
police that there was two gentlemen
that word dresses police officers that
went to the building of Isabelle Stewart
they ran the arraignment doorbell and
they said there is a disturbance of
teenagers we heard around the building
we just want to make sure that
everything's okay the security guard
said well I'm not really supposed to
allow anyone end but I will like allow
this because you're police officers
which is insane and he said mr.
buh-buh-buh-buh there's a warrant out
for your arrest you're under arrest for
the blah blah blah blah blah and he was
like soup that he was like okay like
someone's happening so I got a like kind
of say hey what's going on
so he moved and as soon as he moved
there boom boom boom cackling what was
so crazy was okay they like called the
other guy on security they had him call
on security and say you you need to come
down here something's happening like
so this guy came in
so they taped my bubble of duct tape and
mouse they realized that Isabelle was so
smart in her time that she like
literally like secured the art to the
wall we got to get out of there so what
was even crazier was they took a knife
and just went like crazy you know like
they were just like good they were like
idiots things cut it out and we're like
Canal Street New York why they took our
razor blade yes I mean like thug like
nation
so these guys go through like hundreds
and millions of dollars but hard so this
FBI guy came in and people were recorded
these guys were like around 35 years old
like 510 like they these policemen that
got in this car and say like you know
what I mean like it's crazy
he's like I've seen Rembrandt's appear
at these Chinese restaurants in the
bathroom before or I've been in Paris
where I've been at this underground
tunnel and there's been a picture of
Monet so what was even crazier was every
lead was dead dead dead dead dead and he
was just like I have never experienced
something like this I am never like ever
in my life not been able to follow up
because he used to be he worked for the
FBI he worked in the art theft situation
the art has never resurfaced ever in its
time and we're just so rare that like 22
years with the five million dollar
reward somebody somewhere in some
Southie place is holding that Rembrandt
up in some frame somewhere and that's
what's happening they were either idiots
they were con men they were just stupid
or they were brilliant but they never
made it to the fourth floor because
that's where all the expensive art was
you